

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Javascript / Next.Js / ReactJs / VueJs PHP / Laravel / Slim Nodejs / ExpressJS Sequelize / Objection.js, Mongoose (Nodejs ORM), CSS / SASS, HTML MySQL, MongoDB Kubernetes, Docker

More skills https://md-adil.github.io/me/#detailed-skills

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

C#
Python
C / C++ / QT
Java
Bash
Time management
Team player
Fast learner
Motivated

DEVELOPMENT TOOLS

Git Webpack / Gulp Sublime Text Vim Visual Studio Code Atom

DESIGNING TOOLS

Photoshop Illustrator Adobe Premier

MD ADIL

DEGREE DON'T DEFINE SKILLS

ABOUT

Love to code.

Code enthusiast

Self taught computer programer.

Always enjoy new technologies and connect with people.

PERSONAL PROJECT

YACS (https://yacs.in)

Talk to anyone without sharing contacts.

- Tech stack: React, Node, MongoDB, Redis
- Has been created during lockdown leave

Recent most downloaded open-source project for React and Typescript www.npmjs.com/package/react-read-otp weekly downloads more thant 1.2k

WORK EXPERIENCE

SR. SOFTWARE ARCHITECT

Bajaj Finserv Health (https://www.bajajfinservhealth.in/) | JAN 2022 - Present

- Backend & Frontend architecture
- Performance Optimisation
- Security
- DevOps (Azure services, Kubernetes, Docker)
- Organisation wide coding guidelines and Code.

SR. SOFTWARE ENGINEER - LEAD

Bajaj Finserv Health (https://www.bajajfinservhealth.in/) | OCT 2020 - JAN 2022

- Fullstack development
- Frontend architect
- Squad Lead

SR. SOFTWARE ENGINEER - LEAD

BigRadar (https://www.bigradar.io/) | Apr 2017 - Present

- Responsible for entire technical decision and codes written for BigRadar
- Tech Stack: Node.js, React, Typescript, MongoDB, MySQL, Redis

CONTACT

P: +91 9818128797 P: +91 7503997978 E: adil.sudo@gmail.com W: http://md-adil.github.io/

SOCIAL

https://www.linkedin.com/in/md-adil/ https://github.com/md-adil https://www.npmjs.com/~adil.sudo

CTO & CO-FOUNDER

Bigly Technologies | Mar 2017 - Oct 2020

- Helping team to choose relevant technologies and framework
- Solve engineering problems
- Tech Stack: PHP, Laravel, MySQL, Redis

SR. SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Edunuts (http://www.edunuts.com/) | Aug 2015 - Apr 2017

- Managing and improving the company's tech stack by choosing relevant technologies and frameworks.
- Assigning sprints to each team member
- Optimizing the performance and security of the website
- R&D for future features
- Tech Stack: PHP, Laravel, Slim, MySQL, Node.js, MongoDB

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF COMMERCE

University of Delhi | 2010 - 2013

HOBBIES

Computers and Only Computers Movies Solving Puzzles

SALARY AND EXPECTATION

Expected Negotiation